PROFESSOR: OK today we're going to
be talking about informed search.
And informed search is about taking the
kinds of search problems we had
from last lecture and injecting into
them information about where the goals
might be so that we can find optimal
solutions while exploring less of the
search tree.
So the outline for today is we're going
to talk about the key ingredient
of informed search, which is
the idea of a heuristic.
We're going to use this heuristics in
a simple way for greedy search and
then we're going to put all of these
ideas we have together for the kind of
pinnacle of our search unit,
which is a star search.
Then we're going to go back and talk
about a small but very important
change to how we do search,
called graph search.
Which makes the tree search we have
already much more efficient by
avoiding duplicated work.